To connect to Microsoft Teams
from the Session Details page,
make sure Microsoft Teams
is selected in the Connection Type box.
Then click Connect.
Your browser may display a dialogue
telling you the page is trying
to open the Microsoft Teams app.
If you want to use Teams on the web,
click Cancel.
Otherwise, click Open.
You'll then be taken to the
Join Conversation page.
This page offers three different options
to join the meeting.
First, you can download
the Microsoft Teams app.
After installation, the app
will launch automatically.
Second, you can open
Microsoft Teams in your browser.
Third, you can open the meeting
in the app if it's already installed.
If it's your first time using Teams
in the browser,
click Allow when prompted
to use your microphone and camera.
You'll also have the option
to dial in to a meeting.
The Session Details page contains
a link to dial-in numbers by country.
To join by phone, make a note
of the Conference ID.
It is made up of nine digits.
For the best experience,
sign in with your Learnlight account.
Without signing in, browser options
are limited.
To sign in, click the link
at the bottom of the page
before joining a meeting.
By signing in, the experience
is similar to the desktop app.
Please note: these features
are not available in the browser:
The option to change or blur
your background,
live captions,
and the back and forward arrows.